live.
Welcome brothers and sisters to another
Wednesday question and answer where we
open up with the 10 Commandments that
God commanded for the whole world to
keep. Brother Tanzel.
And God spake all these words saying, I
am the Lord thy God, which have brought
thee out of the land of Egypt, out of
the house of bondage. Thou shalt have no
other gods before me.
Thou shalt not make unto thee any graven
image, or any likeness of anything that
is in heaven above, or that is in earth
beneath, or that is in the water under
the earth. Thou shalt not bow down
thyself to them, nor serve them. For I
the Lord thy God am a jealous God,
visiting the iniquity of the fathers
upon the children unto the third and
fourth generation of them that hate me,
and showing mercy unto thousands of them
that love me, and keep my commandments.
Thou shalt not take the name of the Lord
thy God in vain.
For the Lord will not hold him guiltless
that taketh his name in vain.
Remember the sabbath day, to keep it
holy.
Six days shalt thou labor, and do all
thy work: but the seventh day is the
sabbath of the Lord thy God: in it thou
shalt not do any work, thou, nor thy
son, nor thy daughter, thy manservant,
nor thy maidservant, nor thy cattle, nor
thy stranger that is within thy gates:
For in six days the Lord made heaven and
earth, the sea, and all that in them is,
and rested the seventh day: wherefore
the Lord blessed the sabbath day, and
hallowed it.
Honour thy father and thy mother: that
thy days may be long upon the land which
the Lord thy God giveth thee.
Thou shalt not kill. Thou shalt not
commit adultery.
Thou shalt not steal.
Thou shalt not bear false witness
against thy neighbour. Thou shalt not
covet thy neighbour's house, thou shalt
not covet thy neighbour's wife, nor his
manservant, nor his maidservant, nor his
ox, nor his ass, nor any thing that is
thy neighbour's.
We read Exodus 20:1 through 17, and may
the Lord have a blessing to the reading
of his words. In Jesus' name we pray.
Amen.
So here on question and answer you can
ask us a question and we'll answer it
according to the King James Bible. And
if we cannot find the answer, we will
seek further counsel to bring you an
answer at a later time.
The questions we will not answer are the
long scripture questions, as well as the
vague questions, and questions of
debate. We are not here to debate, we're
here to spread the true gospel of Jesus.
So please be as direct as possible with
your questions so we can be as direct as
possible with our answers out of the
King James Bible. No other Bibles or
books will be acknowledged on this
program. Also keep in mind this is a
live stream, so feel free to send in
your questions that pertain to
everlasting life. We just ask that you
keep them to a two scripture maximum.
Let me introduce you to family that's on
the panel this evening. Brother Jerome.
Grace and peace.
Brother Julius. Good evening, everybody.
Brother Dre.
Good evening.
Brother Tanzel.
Sister Deborah.
Good evening.
Brother Sean.
And we have the guest caller with us,
and I'm brother Cornell. What is our
first question of the evening?
Yes, there are several held over
questions that will be answered first
before getting into tonight's Q&A. Um
Valencia, your question
uh was is this Jesus speaking about
Israel, Zechariah 13 verses 6 through 8?
Uh that answer That question was
answered last week on Thursday Q&A
atonement. So check uh that
uh
uh time last Thursday
Q&A atonement.
Your question was answered there. So
moving on, the next question from
Shirley Haney Stabular,
she says, "Please explain Hebrew 9
verses 6 through 8. I thought I heard
brother Bowie say there were only one
tabernacle, but I see first and second.
Please explain so I can understand what
was said. Thanks."
All right. And she wanted to know about
Hebrews 9 verse 6 through 8.
Yes.
All right. Why don't we go there,
Brother Tanzel? Hebrews 9:6-8.
And the guest caller,
I'm going to ask him to
represent Brother Bowie for this
question.
Hebrews 9, pick it up at verse 6.
Now when these things were thus
ordained,
the priests went always into the first
tabernacle, accomplishing the service of
God.
But into the second went the high priest
alone once every year,
but not without blood, which he offered
for himself,
and for the errors of the people:
The Holy Ghost this signifying that the
way into the holiest of all was not yet
made manifest,
while as the first tabernacle was yet
standing:
Okay, the first thing is
he had with the the the one that wrote
this,
he
confused if uh uh the holy and and
most holy place
with tabernacle.
First thing is, before we go any
further, I want to show you what
what was said when he was telling about
this.
Uh
he's kind of defined it explained it.
Start at verse four.
Start reading.
In fact, read verse one first. Then
we're going to skip down to verse four.
Okay.
Then verily the first covenant had also
ordinances of divine service, and a
worldly sanctuary.
Now, he's letting you know that what was
on earth,
it was divine, but it was in a worldly
sanctuary. Skip down to verse six and
we're going to uh five and we're going
to pay attention to what he said here.
Go ahead.
And over it the cherubims of glory
shadowing the mercy seat:
Of which we cannot now speak
particularly.
Now, let me say he he went and explained
all of that stuff and he got on to the
shadowing of the mercy seat, he said,
"Of which we cannot
we cannot
uh now speak particularly." That mean he
he couldn't be
specific.
You understand?
You know what we're going to do is we're
going to go back and look at it and show
you that
there was no first and second
tabernacle.
There was a
holy place and most holy place.
Let's go back to uh Exodus,
40th chapter,
and we're going to read eight uh uh
uh
verse 18,
and we're going to skip down to 20 and
21.
Okay, read it when you get there.
Exodus 40 and verse 18.
And Moses reared it reared up the
tabernacle, and he fastened his sockets,
and set up the boards thereof,
and put in the bars thereof, and reared
up his pillars.
Now, he said reared up the tabernacle,
didn't he? Right.
Didn't say more than
first and second.
He just reared up the tabernacle. Skip
down to verse 20 20 and read 20 and 21.
And he took and put the testimony into
the ark,
and set the staves on the ark, and put
the mercy seat above upon the ark.
And he brought the ark into the
tabernacle, and set up the veil of the
covering,
and covered the ark of the testimony; as
the Lord commanded Moses.
So now, he's still talking about the
tabernacle. So he came in with a veil.
And he covered the ark. Now let's go
into Exodus the 26th chapter,
and we're going to read verse 30 and 31.
Read it when you get there.
And thou shalt rear up the tabernacle
according to the fashion thereof which
was shewed thee in the mount.
And thou shalt make a veil of blue, and
purple, and scarlet, and fine twined
linen of cunning work: With cherubims
shall it be made:
Uh-huh.
And thou shalt hang it upon four pillars
of shittim wood overlaid with gold, and
their hooks shall be of gold, upon four
sockets of silver.
Go ahead. And thou shalt hang up the
veil under the taches,
that thou mayest bring in thither within
the veil the ark of the testimony: And
the veil shall divide unto you between
the holy place
and the most holy.
See, that's what he's talking about,
that veil. There ain't no first and
second tabernacle.
He's got your veil in there, and that
veil is separate between the
holy and the most holy place. Right. Did
you finish that?
Yeah.
See, and what happens is
every year,
every day, priests went before the veil
in the holy place and sprinkled the
blood of the sacrifice.
But only once a year, he went behind or
within the veil.
And that's on the day of atonement.
Let's go in Leviticus the 16th chapter
and read verse two.
And the Lord spake unto Moses,
saying unto Aaron thy brother, that he
come not at all times into the holy
place within the veil before the mercy
seat,
which is upon the ark, that he die not,
and I will appear in the cloud upon the
mercy seat.
Now, he tell him he not could don't come
at all times Right.
into the veil, didn't it?
Before the mercy seat.
Most holy place, unless he die.
So, now, so, in Hebrews, like I said,
they said they weren't particular quite
weren't so particular in other words,
they weren't
they didn't have specific understanding.
Apparently, the uh uh
uh uh
the tabernacle of the congregation
had been removed.
And so, they didn't know particularly
what it was. So, they instead of going
back,
so, when he was saying the first
tabernacle and the second tabernacle, it
was not but one tabernacle.
Right. But inside the tabernacle, you
had a veil that was separating
the holy the holy place from the most
holy place.
And every day,
you went into the uh uh uh
holy place and sprinkled the blood of
the sacrifice
before the veil.
But only once a year, on the day of
atonement, you went within the veil.
That's behind the veil into the most
holy place, and you sprinkled the blood
over uh the veil. So, it wasn't but one
tabernacle.
There were one but one tabernacle. Now,
I want to throw this in. Maybe somebody
can pull it up. You know, when Israel
when the Lord got uh when Moses had to
move the tabernacle,
He had to pitch it outside the camp.
And pitch it outside the camp. Grab that
right quick.
All right. Let me search mobile for
that.
I think that's Exodus 33 and 7.
Yes, sir.
>> Exodus 30
33 and 7?
That's when the Lord got mad with
Israel?
Yeah.
>> He was not going to go He wasn't going
to go up among them anymore?
Right. Yeah, you can pick it up at six.
Yeah.
He said he was going to send his angel
before,
but he was not going to go up before us.
What you say you started at?
Verse six.
Okay.
Um
Exodus 33 and 6.
Yeah, I was looking at verse five. It
kind of bring in more introduction, but
I start at six.
Yeah, five five is a good pick up. Pick
it up at five, Tanzael. Go ahead.
And the Lord said unto Moses, say unto
the children of Israel, ye are
stiff-necked people. I will come up into
the midst of thee in a moment and
consume thee.
Therefore, now put off thy or- ornaments
from thee, that I may know what to do
unto thee. And the children of
Israel stripped themselves of their
ornaments by the mount Horeb. And Moses
took the tabernacle and pitched it
without the camp, afar off from the
camp. And called it the tabernacle of
the congregation. And it came to pass
that everyone which sought the Lord went
out unto the tabernacle of the
congregation, which was without the
camp.
So, now, there was one tabernacle,
wasn't it?
Right.
So,
inside that tabernacle,
you had a veil.
In the front of that veil was the holy
place,
and in the back of that veil, behind the
veil, or within the veil was the most
holy place. So, it wasn't two
tabernacles.
It's just the way it was written down
there, and the guy already said, which
we ain't too particular about.
Okay? One tabernacle
with the holy and most holy place.
That's all I have to say.
All right.
We hope that answered your question as
we move on to our next one.
Next one. Queen Kelly asked for you to
explain the moon cycle and how the days
are counted in regards to what day we
observe the memorial of trumpets and
then the day of atonement.
All right, the moon cycle and how the
days are counted in regards to the
trumpets and atonement. Brother Jerome.
Well, uh the new moon is the beginning
of your months. It's it's the and it
starts the first day
of the month. It's the new moon. Okay?
So, let's go to uh Numbers
28.
And we going to do we going to do First
Samuel after that, Tanzael.
Numbers 28 verse one and two, and we
going to skip.
You get it, go ahead.
All right, Numbers 28.
Yeah.
Um One and two.
And the Lord spake unto Moses, saying,
command the children of Israel and say
unto them, my offering and my bread for
my sacrifice made by fire, for a sweet
savor unto me,
shall ye observe to offer unto me in
their due season. Due season. Skip down
to verse 11.
And in the beginning of your months, ye
shall offer burnt offering unto the
Lord,
two young bullocks and one ram, seven
lambs of the first year without spot.
Okay. We don't do the sacrifices no
more, but I wanted you to read it said
in beginning of your months.
That's the new moon. So, now we going to
go to Samuel
and and put it together. So, go to First
Samuel chapter 20. It's going to talk
about a time where they were dealing
with the new moon, and it's going to
kind of establish what day of the month
the new moon is.
Okay? So, go to uh First Samuel chapter
and read verse five and then we going to
skip.
And David said unto Jonathan, behold,
tomorrow is the new moon.
And I shall not fail to sit with the
king at meat. But let me go that I may
hide myself in the field unto the third
day at evening.
Okay, skip down to verse 24.
And David hid himself in the field, and
when the new moon was come, the king sat
him down to eat meat. All right, he
said, now when the new moon was come, he
sat down
to eat meat, okay? Now, skip and read
verse 27.
And it came to pass on the morrow,
which was the second day of the month,
Mhm. that David's place was empty, and
Saul said unto Jonathan, his son,
wherefore cometh not the son of Jesse to
meat neither yesterday nor today?
Okay, so, the second day
of the month is not the new moon.
The first day of the month
is the new moon. That's the beginning of
your months, okay? You don't see nothing
at all, no slits or nothing. It's it's
dark.
All right, that's your first day of the
month. Now,
um
how do we put that together? You had a
second part of this question,
uh so we can
determine when we keep the blowing of
the trumpets
and so on so forth.
Let's deal with that.
Um
Now,
we go by the new moons that's in
Jerusalem.
Okay? And that's how we set our dates
for the
high days that you find in Leviticus the
23rd chapter, okay? All right. So, let's
go look at that cuz in in in Jerusalem,
uh
on September the 21st, it was 10:55
p.m.
All right?
That's night time, right? But in
Chicago,
it was daytime. So, we we we can't start
it right away. We have to wait till the
sun go down, all right?
So, in Jerusalem, it went down uh uh the
new moon was the 21st of September, all
right? We going to start
uh on the 22nd. Okay?
When it when the sun go down, all right?
So, now, let's go look at this Leviticus
23.
Yeah. Cuz the 22nd, that's going to be
your first day
of the seventh month, which is when we
celebrate the blowing of
uh the trumpets,
if I'm not mistaken. Let's go read it so
I can get it right.
Okay, Leviticus 23 and 23.
Yeah, Leviticus 23 and 23.
And the Lord spake unto Moses, saying,
speak unto the children of Israel,
saying,
in the seventh month, in the first day
of the month, shall ye have a sabbath, a
memorial of blowing of trumpets, and
holy convocation.
Yeah. So, we celebrate that on on the
22nd when the sun went down.
All right?
So, now
read that Did you read that Did you read
You finished that 24, right? Mhm.
All right. So, now on the 10th day
of that same month, the Hebrew months,
all right?
Then we dealt with the next feast day
which was the atonement. Right. Okay?
So, now
on our calendar, that's October
the 2nd.
When the sun went down
October
the 1st. Soon as the sun go down October
the 1st, that's a new day. Starting in
the evening. So, now it's the 20 Now
it's the Now it's the 2nd, all right?
So, we kept Right. So, we kept the
atonement
on the October the 2nd.
Okay?
That's all I got on if anybody want to
add something.
All right.
Thank you for that. Hope that answered
their question as we move on to our next
one.
Next one, Lovey says, "If a young man
died without circumcision,
will he make it in the kingdom of God?"
All right, brother Julius. We know quite
a few people have died without
circumcision. Will they make it into the
kingdom of God?
That is a God question, but I'm going to
I'm going to take a shot at it according
to scripture. Uh we know we had two
great baby killings
uh in the days of Mo Moses and in the
days of Herod. Now, the midwives
wouldn't kill the babies, but when
Pharaoh put his people out uh to kill
the Hebrew women that had babies, as
soon as them babies were born, they
threw them them babies possibly into the
Nile river.
And so, they uh if they were cuz
typically, you're supposed to circumcise
at 8 days old. But,
uh I got two scriptures that kind of
deal with this. Let's go into
uh
Romans, the 9th chapter.
Cuz the child ain't did nothing.
Romans chapter 9, brother Tenzel.
And will you please read verse 15? Look
what the Lord told Moses. Paul's going
to quote Exodus, the 33rd chapter
uh at verse 19. And Paul's going to tell
uh Moses
uh
uh I'm sorry. Uh Moses going to go right
back to uh Paul's going right back to
Moses, right?
When you get it, brother, go ahead,
Tenzel. Exodus 9 and 15. Look what he
said.
Well, he said to Moses,
"I will have mercy on whom I will have
mercy. Uh-huh. I will have compassion on
whom I will have compassion." One more
spot. Revelation, the 20th chapter.
Cuz
the children might not have been
circumcised. We don't know the reasons
why.
That's why I went to that first
scripture.
And this is what gives me great hope
that that uh they will be in the kingdom
of God. Revelation 20 and verse 6.
When Go ahead, brother.
Blessed and holy is he that hath part in
the first resurrection.
On such the second death have no power.
Uh-huh. But they shall be priests of God
and of Christ. And shall reign with him
a thousand years. So, we got the
resurrection to look forward to. That's
all I got. Anybody want to add to that?
It all depends, too,
on whether you know or not.
It's just like the Pharisee said, "I
can't say it right now." What Jesus
said, he said, "You said you know,
therefore you're guilty." Yeah.
He so, if you don't know about it
and don't understand that you have to be
that have to be done, it's just like
anything else.
The Lord don't
The Lord don't cover the The blood of
Jesus don't cover the blood of willful
sinning.
He cover the blood
if you sin in ignorance. Yes. And that
burden. Bless you.
God is God is a fair God. If you don't
know,
the Holy Holy Ghost you. But if you do
know and refuse to do it, he hold it
against you.
Yes.
Yeah.
All right.
>> There's a uh
a place in Revelation, the 14th chapter,
uh
I know that we said that was when these
could be babies.
They could be.
Um
I'll read it at the See what you guys
think. Uh Revelation 14 and I start at
four.
But these are they which were not
defiled with women.
For they are virgins.
And these are they which follow the lamb
whithersoever he goeth.
And these were redeemed from among men,
being the firstfruits unto God and unto
the lamb.
And in their mouth was found no guile,
for they are without fault before the
throne of God.
So,
these could have been
you know, some babies.
You know, cuz when you think of
their mouth was found no guile. There
ain't no person in found no mouth with
no guile but Jesus. So.
Yeah. And um
like we said, once you know and you
choose not to do, then the Lord got
written in here,
you'll be without excuse.
Okay.
All right. Hope that answered your
question as we continue to move on.
Moving on, Elaine Brown asks, "If an
elderly sick person asks to be on
hospice and asks for morphine, is this
considered suicide?"
All right, brother Dre. Elderly person
asks to be on hospice and morphine, is
that considered suicide?
No.
No, it's not.
Hospice is when a patient is given
specialized care
when they have a terminal illness. You
know, they
focus on focusing on managing
the symptoms rather than curing the
illness. So,
under hospice,
you know, they give them things that
will comfort them while they're going
through pain.
You know, sometimes morphine is one of
the things that's given.
But uh
you know, they're not giving it they
don't give it to them to
you know, unalive or kill them.
So,
it's just a a medicine to comfort them
and give them relief in their pain.
Let's go to one scripture. Let's go to
Proverbs, 31st chapter
and look at something here.
Proverbs 31 and we're going to read
verses 6 and 7.
When you get it, go ahead, brother.
Give strong drink unto him that is ready
to perish.
And wine unto those that be of heavy
hearts. Mhm. Let him drink and forget
his poverty
and remember his misery no more.
Yeah, even back then, they had strong
drink, you know,
for those that
were ready to perish.
Even in Timothy, it says,
"Drink no longer water,
but use a little wine for stomach's sake
and thine often infirmities."
Right. So, you know,
morphine is a medication that comforts
people when they are in pain. It's not
it's not set to for them to die. So, no,
they're not committing suicide. That's
all I got. Pain medicine.
Yeah. That's right, Dre.
I tell you, pain can be so tough, you'll
be looking for some relief. That's
right. Pain medicine. You know. All
right. Thank you for that, brother. Hope
that answered their question as we move
on to our next one.
Next one, Sheaquilla Akujo B asks, "How
do you treat a poor function around a
loved one who has antichrist
spirit?"
Uh 1 John 4,
verses 2 and 3 are given.
All right. How do you function around
somebody
with a bad spirit? All right, brother
Jerome.
[Music]
Uh let's go read the verse they gave.
1 John
chapter 4, verse 2 and 3.
Hereby know ye the spirit of God. Every
spirit that confesseth that Jesus Christ
is come in the flesh is of God.
And every spirit that confesseth not
that Jesus Christ is come in the flesh
is not of God.
And this is that spirit of antichrist.
Whereof we have heard that it should
come and even now already is in the
world.
Okay.
So, I'd like to I'd like to share Romans
12 with you.
Uh let's go to Romans 12 and we're going
to read verse 17
through
20.
Romans, the 12th chapter.
16 through 20.
Say it again verses
uh
17 through 20.
Recompense to no man evil for evil.
Provide things honest in the sight of
all men.
And if it be possible as much as life in
you, live peaceably with all men.
But dearly beloved, avenge not
yourselves, but rather give place unto
wrath. For it is written,
vengeance is mine. I will repay, saith
the Lord.
So therefore, if thine enemy hunger,
feed him. If he thirst, give him drink.
For in so doing, thou shalt heap coals
of fire on his head.
Okay.
Be not overcome of evil, but overcome
evil with good. Yeah. That's all I got.
If anybody want to add, they can.
All right.
And pray and pray. As we continue to
move on to our next question.
Yes, moving on.
D. Johnson
uh says, I have a few, but it is a
several culinary questions. So I'm going
to read them quickly and then I'll go
separately
uh
uh for each one. So the question is one,
can I cook fry with beef tallow or
tallow from any clean animal?
Uh two, can I eat serve use caviar
uh from a clean fish? Uh three, can I
fry
or saute my sushi as long as there is no
shellfish
and is only includes clean fish such as
salmon or tuna, seaweed, veggies and
rice. So here's number one question
again.
Can I cook fry with beef tallow or
tallow from any clean animal?
All right, brother Julius.
All right, uh beef tallow is the
animal fat. It is the fat of
uh ox or cow or or or deer or whatever.
It is the fat that's around the kidneys.
Or or certain organs.
That is the what that is what tallow is.
It is animal fat. And so you want to
whoever they want to know can they cook
or fry. I like the the idea that you say
cook or fry. But let's go look what the
book say at this first one. Let's go
brother Tazadaq, give us Genesis seventh
chapter.
Genesis seventh chapter. Genesis chapter
seven. Beef tallow is animal fat just
like lard is pork fat or swine fat.
Look what the Lord said. Because the and
the other question is
if it's a clean any clean animal. What
the book say? Leviticus
7 and 22. Go ahead, brother. And the
Lord spake unto Moses saying,
speaking to the children of Israel
saying,
Ye shall eat no manner of fat of ox or
of sheep or of goat. Those are clean
beasts.
You shall eat no manner of fat of ox or
clean beasts or of of goat. Go ahead.
And the fat of the beast that dieth of
itself, and the fat of that which is
torn with beasts, may be used in any
other use, but ye shall not in no wise
eat of it. So now, if it's cooked in an
animal fat
you're still eating it.
Even though it's a clean beast, it's
still it's still it's just like when you
eat uh pork skins, that is cooked in the
fat and you're eating the fat. That's
what skins are
uh
that's what those fats are in that
particular case. Now
uh what's the next one, Debbie?
The next one is, can I eat
or serve or use caviar from a clean
fish?
Caviar is fish eggs.
But you got to it could be the fish eggs
of salmon tuna
cod trout, flounder
or groupers or such as what sea bass. So
now it's but caviar is meant to be eaten
raw.
But you can cook the eggs
if it's if you cook it, they have a
thing called fried fish eggs.
Now
that's the answer to that right there.
You got to cook it. Because it's got
impurities in it. But if it's clean, you
can fry you can fry it.
But caviar really is is fish eggs.
Mhm. Got to be cooked.
As a kid, I used to eat brains and eggs
in Arkansas. Cow brains and eggs.
Oh good.
Old school. Go ahead. What's the next
one? Okay, the next one. Can I fry or
saute my sushi as long as there is no
shellfish
and is only include clean fish such as
salmon or tuna, seaweed, veggies and fry
and rice.
Sushi is
simply
vinegared rice.
Everything else is added to it like
salmon or squid or octopus or
catfish, whatever it is. But sushi
itself is just and yes, you can use the
sushi itself because it is is vinegared
seasoned rice. That's all it is. Now
what what what makes it unclean is
whatever you add to it in terms of
unclean.
So as long as you
uh
cook it.
You said can you cook or fry with it? Or
whatever the case.
>> Fry or or saute. Saute, you know you
know, you
as long as it's you know, again
seaweed all everything else is added to
it. But in of itself, sushi is just
vinegared rice. Everything else is added
to it.
I hope that help. I hope that help.
I'm not a chef or cook. I just do my
best to stick with what I said the Lord
in Leviticus 20
11th chapter.
Yeah. I want to add something.
No, he just wanted like you say, cook it
cuz you want to make sure ain't no blood
in it. Yeah. And shellfish is like
shrimp uh crab, lobster, what else?
Oysters, mussels and clams.
Mhm. Well, that's not clean. They
neither do they have uh uh
uh Listen.
>> Guest caller.
Question was, can you do that with clean
fish? The answer is yes. Yeah.
Now, we should move on. Yes, sir.
Sister Debbie, our next question. Yes,
moving on. Sai Amul
Amaroo Israel asks, who are the 24
elders and four beasts mentioned in
Revelation chapter four?
All right, let's go to Revelation
chapter four, Tenzel.
And when we get there, the guest caller
uh take it from there and the verse he
like to start.
Okay.
Revelation 4 1 and 1 1 and 2 first.
So this show you this is the throne of
the Lord. This is Jesus' throne. Go
ahead.
And after this, I looked and behold, a
door was opened in heaven. And the first
voice which I heard was as it were a
trumpet talking with me, which said,
come up hither and I will show thee
things which must be hereafter.
Now, those are the things must be
hereafter because what it is is Jesus'
kingdom is hereafter.
Now, he was around his throne. Was that
was that verse two? Did you read verse
No, that was verse one.
Read verse two.
And immediately I was in the spirit. And
behold, a throne was set in heaven. And
one sat on the throne.
Now, it says in heaven, but that's
talking about Jesus' kingdom when it's
come. He said, you know
he saw this vision in heaven, but it's
for the future because it said
hereafter. Now, what's around that
throne? Verse four, read it.
And around about the throne were four
and 20 seats.
And upon the seats I saw four and 20
elders sitting clothed in white raiment.
And they had on their heads crowns of
gold.
So that's in that's and that is the time
of the millennium period. Get down to
verse six and what else was around the
throne?
And before the throne there was a sea of
glass like into crystal.
And in the midst of the throne and
roundabout the throne
were four beasts full of eyes before and
behind.
And the first Were these
Did you finish it? Yeah.
Okay. First thing we're going to do with
the 24 elders
is going to 1 Chronicles
24th chapter.
We're going to read one
and we're going to skip down to five.
Then we're going to skip down
and go from 7 to 18.
First
1 Chronicles 24:1.
Now these are the division of the sons
of Aaron.
The sons of Aaron, Nadab and Abihu,
Eleazar and Ithamar.
Now these are the sons of Aaron. Skip
down to verse five and read it.
Thus were they divided by lot, one sort
with another.
For the governors of the sanctuary and
governors of the house of God were of
the sons of Eleazar and of the sons of
Ithamar.
Now these are the governors of the house
of God.
Now let's go and get to and see how many
of them are it is.
We're going to read from 7 to to 18.
Just keep reading.
Now the first lot
Okay.
Now the first lot came forth of
Jehoiarib, the second of Jedaiah.
The third of Harim
the fourth to Seorim
and the fifth to Malchijah
the sixth to Mijamin, the seventh to
Hakkos, the eighth to Abijah, the ninth
to Jeshua, the tenth
to Shecaniah the eleventh to Eliashib
Elisha, the twelfth to Jacob
the thirteenth to Hezir, and the
fourteenth to Jeshebeab.
And the fifteenth to Bilgah, and the
sixteenth
to Immer.
The
the fifteenth
Okay, the fifteenth to Bilgah and the
sixteenth to Immer, the seventeenth to
Hezir and the eighteenth
to
Aphses
the nineteenth to Pethahiah
and the twentieth to
Hezekiah.
The one and twentieth to Jachin and two
and twentieth to Gamul.
The three and twentieth to Delaiah, the
fourth and twentieth to Maaziah.
These were the orders of them in their
service to come into the house
of the Lord according to their manner as
upon Aaron their father as the Lord of
God of Israel had commanded him.
Now so the 24 elders are the sons of
Aaron
and we even know their name.
So they come so those are the sons of
Aaron.
They're all priests and they're going to
be governors of the house of God.
That's why they're sitting on
uh
24 thrones
and all of them have crowns.
So they're going to be governors of the
house of the Lord while while the
millennium period is going on. They're
going to be in the first resurrection.
As far as the
four
uh beasts are concerned
these are
angels, cherub angels.
And let's see when they were
brought around God's throne cuz they
were around the throne too.
Let's go into Genesis third chapter
read from verse 22 to 24.
And the Lord God said, "Behold, the man
is become as one of us to know good and
evil. And now lest he put forth his hand
and take also of the tree of life and
eat and live forever."
Therefore the Lord God sent him forth
from the garden of Eden to till the
ground from whence he was taken.
So he drove out the man and he placed at
the east of the garden of Eden cherubims
and a flaming sword which turned every
way to keep the way of the tree of life.
So now these cherub angels, they weren't
to keep the way of the garden of Eden,
they were to keep the way of the tree of
life.
And Jesus is the tree of life. Right.
Yeah.
>> They were
cherub angels. So now
let's go into Psalm
99 because every time Yeshua Jesus
throne these guys are there.
Psalm
uh 99.
And one.
Read it when you get there.
The Lord reigneth. Let the people
tremble.
He sitteth between the cherubims.
Let the earth be moved.
So
from the time of Adam and Eve
the Lord have had them cherubs around
him.
And
let's go into Ezekiel
first chapter.
We're going to read one and then we're
going to skip down.
Ezekiel 1.
Now it came to pass in the thirteenth
year, in the fourth month, and the
fifteenth day of the month as I was
among the captives by the river of
Chebar that the heavens were opened and
I saw visions of God.
Now he saw he saw the Lord on his
throne. Skip down to verse four, read
from four to seven.
And I looked and behold a whirlwind
came out of the north
a great cloud and fire enfolding itself
and a brightness was about it. And out
of the midst thereof as the color of
amber and out of the midst of the fire.
Also out of the midst thereof came the
likeness of four living creatures.
And this was their appearance. They had
the likeness of a man and everyone had
four faces.
And everyone had four wings.
And their feet were straight feet and
the soles of their feet was like the
soles of a calf's foot.
And they sparkled like the color of
burnished brass.
Now
it was four of
and all of them and every one of them
had four faces. When you go into
Revelation they just name one of the
faces on each one of them like as a man
an ox
a
eagle
and a
uh a lion.
>> Same one. But now but it says four of
them.
Let's make sure we know what these
angels are called.
Let's go into Ezekiel the tenth chapter
and read verses one through three.
Then I looked and behold in the
firmament that was above the head of the
cherubims there appeared over them as
were a sapphire stone. And as the
appearance of the likeness of a throne.
And he spake unto the man clothed with
linen and said
"Go in between the wheels even under the
cherub
and fill thy hand with coals of fire
from between the cherubs and scatter
them over the city."
And he went
in in my sight.
Now the cherubims stood on the right
side of the house when the man went in
and the clouds filled the inner court.
So now we know that those four
living creatures
are four beasts
they are
four cherub angels
which the Lord put around him
in the garden of Eden
when he drove the man out
to make sure that man didn't have access
to the tree of life.
So that's it in the middle. Let's see.
24 elders are the 24 sons
of Aaron and they're priests
and the
four beasts are four cherub angels.
Yep.
All right.
Hope that answered your question there
as we move on with the time check for
our next one.
Yes, the time is 8:23.
Uh sister Tanisha says, "Can you clarify
Sabbath rules? A sister and I were
talking and we need clarity. We know
there is no cooking or heating food.
When it comes to heating things is food
all we can heat or are we not to iron as
well? Can you clarify this for us,
please?"
All right.
Well, that's good you got understanding
about the cooking and the heating of the
food that you're not to do on the
Sabbath day. And you say when it comes
to heating things is food all
we can heat or are we not to iron as
well?
You know, the Lord has the Sabbath day
set up for us to prepare for it.
Because if we don't prepare for it then
we'll find ourselves sometime the day
before the Sabbath saying, "Okay, my
shirt is wrinkled. I'm not going to iron
it now. I'll wait and iron it on the
Sabbath day." No, you should plan better
than that.
You should be planning for the Lord's
Sabbath day to rest.
Because you got all those 6 days that
you can iron and prepare for the Lord's
Sabbath day.
So, let's go to Isaiah 58.
Cuz this is a very special
day of the week and it is holy
and the Lord calls it a delight.
So, we all have to do it the very best
that we can.
Isaiah 58 and pick it up
at verse 13. Go ahead.
If thou turn away thy foot from the
Sabbath
from doing thy pleasure on my holy day
and call the Sabbath a delight
the holy of the Lord honorable
and shall honor him not doing thy own
ways nor finding thy own pleasures
nor speaking thy own words. Mhm.
Then shall thou delight thyself in the
Lord.
And I will cause thee to ride upon the
high places of the earth
and feed thee with the heritage of Jacob
thy father.
For the mouth of the Lord have spoken
it.
Yes, because you see that the Lord say
that doing thy pleasure on his holy day
and call the Sabbath a delight. We
supposed to look forward to that and be
happy to partake in it and it's holy of
the Lord. And we are supposed to respect
the Lord's Sabbath day and honor him and
not doing our own ways. But, let's go
back to Exodus 16.
Because we should be planning for the
Sabbath day. That should start on the
day before that you are planning.
If you have to iron a shirt, iron it
before the Sabbath kick in.
Don't wait and iron it on the Sabbath
day.
Exodus 16.
And pick it up, brother, at that verse
21.
22. Go ahead, verse 22. Exodus 16 and
22. Cuz the Lord is giving us here this
is a planning session that he wanted
done for his Sabbath day. Go ahead,
brother.
And it came to pass that on the sixth
day they gathered twice as much bread
two omers for one man
and all the rulers of the congregation
came and told Moses. So, this was on the
sixth day that they gathered twice as
much so they wouldn't have to gather
nothing on the Lord's Sabbath day. So,
they planned and the day before the
Sabbath they gathered twice as much so
they would have enough to spill over
into the Sabbath. Go ahead.
And he said unto them, "This is that
which the Lord have said
tomorrow is the rest of the holy Sabbath
unto the Lord. Yeah. Bake that which ye
will bake today and seethe that ye will
seethe that and that which which
remaineth over lay up for you to be kept
until the morning." Because the Lord say
tomorrow is the rest of the holy Sabbath
unto the Lord. So, you got to put your
planning program into effect the day
before.
Go ahead.
And they laid it up till the morning as
Moses bade.
And it did not stink. Neither was there
any worms therein. Uh-huh. And Moses
said, "Eat that today for today is a
Sabbath unto the Lord.
And then ye shall not find it in the
fields.
Six days you shall gather it, but on the
seventh day which is the Sabbath in it
there shall be none."
All right. So, you should um
be planning for the Sabbath day.
Check out your wardrobe. Something need
a little heat on it, go ahead and iron
it before the Sabbath day. Don't wake up
on the Lord's Sabbath day and do that.
Keep that day holy and honorable unto
the Lord.
And that's all I got on that.
And we hope that that answered your
question as we continue to move on to
our next one.
Uh yes, we are
>> Sister Deborah, new territory.
New territory. All right. Uh we are now
into tonight's Q&A for Wednesday,
October the 8th, 2025.
Name says, "Elijah went up in a fiery
horse chariot. So, are there horses in
heaven?
Are there any other animals up there?"
All right. So, we're going to do a
little panel with this question. Sean,
you had a verse for that, right?
Which was John
You had a verse for that?
Uh that John 1
>> Let me Let me Let
The whole thing is
you uh uh uh
as far as horses in heaven you got
angels and angels take all kind of
forms, okay?
Yep. Give you a good example.
First John
1 and 50 1.
And read it.
Saint John. Saint John 1 and 51.
>> Saint John.
John 1.
John 1 and verse 51.
Saint John 1 and 51.
And he said unto him, "Verily, verily, I
say unto you
hereafter you shall see heaven open
and the angels of God ascending and
descending upon the son of man."
Now, I said the angel of God.
Did it look like an angel?
See, when we go to Luke the third
chapter
and uh read verse 22. This is when Jesus
got baptized.
Yep.
When he come up out the water.
And the Holy
Huh?
Luke Luke 3 and 22.
Pick it up at 21.
Now, when all the people were baptized,
it came to pass that Jesus also being
baptized and praying the heaven was
open.
And the Holy Ghost descending in a
bodily shape like a dove upon him. And a
voice came from heaven which said
"Thou art my beloved son
in thee I am well pleased."
So, now
that that that uh uh
that Holy Ghost that came in the bodily
form of a dove, in other words, that
holy angel that come in the bodily form
of a dove.
He was the one that the Lord used to
anoint Jesus. And like Jesus said, "You
going to see the angels ascending and
descending." So, just like that one can
take the form
of a dove angels can take any form. They
can take the form of horses.
I'm not saying that ain't no horses in
heaven, but every time we read the book
it's always talking about God and the
angels.
Right. And see even when Jesus come that
Jesus going to come with all the holy
angels with him.
Even though it looks like uh he's riding
a horse in the 19th chapter of
Revelation
but the whole thing is
it could be a horse
but when I look at most scriptures look
like it all talks about angels to me.
That's the only answer I That's the
answer I give to that question.
Yep. Even them cherubim angels got four
faces.
Yep.
All right.
We're going to leave it right there.
Hope that shine some light on your
question as we move on to our next one.
Uh next one. Andre Jr. ask
"Is it considered evening when it's
pitch black outside or when it's
approaching to be pitch black? For
example, is the considered
evening?"
All right. Guest caller
when is evening?
When you have a person What is it in
Proverbs?
Proverbs 7.
Proverbs 7 and what?
7 and 9.
Go there and read it.
In the twilight, in the evening, in the
black and dark night.
So, that's when your day starts.
In the twilight, in the evening, in the
black and dark night.
So, when it get dark
that is the evening.
Yep.
All right.
Uh when the sun set, now.
Uh-uh. When it get dark. That's why I
had him read that in the twilight, in
the evening, in the black and dark
night. Can't be more specific than that.
Right. That's when the day began.
Evening and the morning is the first
Yep. All right.
Hope that answered your question there
as we move on to our next.
Uh next one. Most Love ask "How do I
know if I'm going through trial and
tribulations?
I try my best to keep the commandments,
but I cry every day because everything
and everyone is against me."
All right. Let's um open that question
up
to the panel.
Hey, can we uh go read uh 1 Peter
the fourth chapter
verse 12 through 14?
All right. You say 1 Peter 12?
Yeah.
The 1 Peter
What chapter?
1 Peter the fourth chapter. Fourth
chapter.
Yeah.
Verse 12.
Yeah, verse 12 through 14.
Beloved,
think it not strange concerning the
fiery trial which is to try you, as
though some strange thing happened unto
you.
Wait.
But rejoice, inasmuch as ye are
partakers of Christ's suffering,
that when his glory shall be revealed,
ye may be glad also with exceeding joy.
Mhm. 14.
If ye be reproached for the name of
Christ, happy are ye, for the spirit of
glory and of God resteth upon you.
On their part he is evil spoken of, but
on your part is glorified. Yeah, and um
read read that Matthew chapter 5 verse
11 and 12.
Blessed are ye, when men shall revile
you, and persecute you, and shall say
all manner of evil against you falsely,
for my
sake.
Rejoice, and be exceeding glad, for
great is your reward in heaven.
For so persecuted they the prophets
which were before you.
Yeah. That's all I got.
Well, you know, if you cry every person
cry every day,
then it depends on what they crying for.
What's the reason for it? They being
persecuted for the word of God,
then there's one thing.
You'll be going through your trial. If
you doing it because the Lord said, you
know, he he
chasteneth all those that he love.
However,
it all depends on why you crying every
day. You could be crying for
for the anything.
So, we can't call this trials and
tribulations for the word of God.
You have to decide that.
Yeah.
You have to say.
All right.
We'll leave it there as we move on to
our next question.
Uh the next one, Most Love also asked,
"What is a wicked person? Wicked seems a
little extreme.
Someone that doesn't keep the Sabbath.
Are they wicked?"
Open to the panel.
Did you say
>> No, they they
they are sinners.
A wicked person is somebody that's doing
that's hurting
that likes to hurt other people that are
hurting other people.
That's a wicked person.
Yeah.
Yeah. Let's go into Psalms 101 and 4.
Psalms 101 and 4.
Psalms 101
and verse 4.
A four line pick it up pick it up uh
hold on, brother. Pick it up at that uh
verse read 3 and 4.
Okay.
I will set no wicked thing before my
eyes.
And I hate the work of them that turn
aside.
It shall not cleave to me.
Mhm. A forward heart shall depart from
me.
I will not know a wicked person.
All right, verse 5.
Whoso privily slandereth his neighbor,
him will I cut off.
Him that hath a high look and a proud
heart will not I suffer.
All right. Anybody else?
Okay. Yes, it's a extreme. If God said
they wicked,
God is the one that call them
uh uh wicked.
Mhm. Can we go and read Ezekiel 18 or or
not?
Yeah, we go there right quick. Ezekiel
18.
Ezekiel 18.
We can pick it up at 26. 26 through uh
28.
When a righteous man turneth away from
his righteousness, and committeth
iniquity, and dieth in them, for his
iniquity that he hath done shall he die.
Again, when the wicked man turneth away
from his wickedness that he hath
committed, and doeth that which is
lawful and right, he shall save a soul
alive.
Because he considereth and turneth away
from all his transgressions that he hath
committed, he shall surely live.
He shall not die.
Mhm.
Yeah. And uh read that 30.
Therefore I will judge you, O house of
Israel, every one according to his ways,
saith the Lord God. Repent, and turn
yourselves from all your transgressions.
So iniquity shall be not your ruin.
Shall not be your ruin.
Yeah.
So.
Always keep that repent.
Hey, always close by.
That's right.
>> All right.
We're going to leave it right there and
move on to our next question.
Uh yes, Sky Rider asked, "Would the Lord
forgive addicts, former addicts that
have been that have relapsed a few
times?" So again,
"Would the Lord forgive addicts, former
addicts that have relapsed a few times?"
I think
uh Julius has mentioned that earlier on
how merciful the Lord is. So, hey,
each individual got to uh make sure he
continue. Let's go to Proverbs 24 and
16.
Proverbs 24 and 16.
Then I got one after that, Cornell.
Yes, sir. Go right ahead, Tenzel.
For a just man falleth seven times, and
riseth up again.
But the wicked shall fall into mischief.
So, you got to hey, keep getting up and
running this race. If you slip and fall,
dust off and get up and keep running.
Absolutely.
The Lord is merciful. What you got,
Julius? Matthew 12 and 1 verse.
Matthew 12.
And 1 verse.
While there's life, there is hope,
sisters and brothers.
You got to recognize you hurting
yourself and other people.
And this
Matthew 12 and 31.
Uh brother T, go ahead.
Wherefore I say unto you, all manner of
sin and blasphemy shall be forgiven unto
men.
But the blasphemy against the Holy Ghost
shall not be forgiven
unto men.
And that
because while there's life, there's
hope. It mentions
uh uh the these things here, but sin
brings on a lot of things, sisters and
brothers.
Bring on addictions, alcoholism,
whatever. These strongholds
uh that hurt yourself and hurt other
people.
But if you repent from and recognize
you know, understand that your body is a
tabernacle
of the
of the Holy Spirit,
turn and turn to him
with uh prayer and repentance.
Hey,
he'll he'll turn to you.
Yeah.
And and and sometime in them cases too,
Julius, sometimes you have to
make sure you you seek some
professional help as well. Sometimes you
can't do it all by yourself. Yeah.
Okay.
All right. We hope that answered your
question as we move on to our next one.
The next one, she said you
Go ahead, Deborah. The next one, uh
Shaniquilla Akujo B asked, "Can you
um
can you help me understand Revelation 3
verse 10? Some say it refers to the
pre-tribulation
rapture,
while others believe it indicates
protection during the current
tribulation we experience now.
Okay. Revelation 3 and 10.
Yes.
All right. Well, we know rapture is not
even in the Bible, so we don't Why you
Read that Revelation 3 and 10, and let's
open it up to the panel. As you tell us
again, Deborah, what it is that they are
seeking. Revelation 3 and 10, Tenzel.
Because thou hast kept the word of my
patience,
I also will keep thee from the hour of
temptation,
which shall come upon all the world to
try them that dwell upon the earth.
This is talking about the great
tribulation
uh you're being protected from the great
tribulation. Mhm.
That terrible time. It has nothing to do
with a pre-tribulation. Has nothing to
do with a rapture, period.
Exactly.
Go go to Revelation 12 and read about
what happened to the woman.
Where she fled to. There you go.
Revelation 12, keep it Tenzel. Mhm.
13. Yep.
And when the dragon saw that he was cast
to the earth,
he persecuted the woman which brought
forth the man child.
And to the woman were given two wings of
a great eagle, that she might fly into
the wilderness, into her place where she
is nourished for a time and times and
half a time from the face of the
serpent.
That is the hour temptation, the great
tribulation, 3 and 1/2 years.
That's where he's going to protect you
with.
On this earth, no rapture.
And uh
please the 91st chapter Psalm 91 and 1.
Read a little of it.
He that dwelleth in the secret place of
the most high shall abide under the
shadow of the almighty.
Go ahead.
I will say of the Lord, he's my refuge
and my fortress, my God, in him will I
trust.
Surely he shall deliver thee from the
snare of the fowler and from the noisome
pestilence.
He shall cover thee with his feathers,
and under his wings shall thou trust.
His truth shall be thy shield and
buckler.
Thou shalt not be afraid
Keep going.
Yep. Yeah. Thou shalt not be afraid for
the terror by night,
nor for the arrow that flieth by day,
nor for the pestilence that walketh in
darkness,
nor for the destruction that wasteth at
noonday.
A thousand shall fall at thy side, and
10,000s at thy right hand. But it shall
not come nigh thee.
Only with thine eyes shalt thou behold
and see
the reward of the wicked.
Now, that's doing the great tribulation.
They got nothing to do with no rapture.
The preachers
preach that you're going to be raptured
out just before the great tribulation.
That's one of the That's one of Gino
Jennings
uh uh uh
teaching, too. But you ain't going
nowhere but to the wilderness. Right. If
you are right
and you know the word of God and you see
the signs.
Yes, sir.
That's the place of safety where the
Lord's going to give his angels charge
over you. And ain't nobody going to come
in, ain't nobody going to hurt you.
But you're not leaving this earth.
You going to a location on this earth
that's called the wilderness. The same
place that Moses dealt with.
Okay.
All right. Hope that answered your
question, Sister Deborah. Time check and
next question.
Yes, the time is 8:46.
IMC asks, "When Jesus returns,
will everybody that is dead be risen? If
not, will the rest be sleeping until the
thousand-year millennium?"
Open to the panel.
Revelation
20th chapter Yep.
Revelation 20 and 4? Yes, sir.
And I saw thrones,
and they that sat upon them,
and judgment was given unto them.
And I saw the souls of them that were
beheaded for the witness of Jesus, and
for the word of God, and which had not
worshipped the beast, neither his image,
neither had received his mark upon their
foreheads or in their hands.
And they lived and reigned with Christ a
thousand years.
Go ahead.
But the rest of the dead lived not again
until the thousand years were finished.
This is the first resurrection.
Blessed and holy is he
>> That's the uh uh uh
Go ahead, finish it.
But blessed and holy is he that hath
part in the first resurrection.
On such the second death have no power.
But they shall be priests of God and of
Christ and shall reign with him a
thousand years.
That's the answer to your question.
Brother the dead
that didn't come up
in that first resurrection, they're
going to remain being dead for another
thousand years.
Don't have to say.
All right.
We're going to move on to our next
question.
Next question.
Laqu Cox says,
"My child My 12-year-old son
was reading Revelation 8 and 9 and asked
if the seven trumpets will all sound in
the same day. Can you help us to
understand?"
All right. The trumpets, the sounding of
the trumpets.
Open to the panel.
What's What's the script they gave?
Revelation 8 Go ahead, Deborah.
Yeah, uh
they gave the chapters, Rever uh
Revelation 8 and Revelation 9. And they
want to know will the seven trumpets,
again, will they all sound in the same
day?
No.
Yeah. Too Too much to fit in one day.
That's the That's the answer to the
question.
The old saying is
uh you you got You got uh uh trumpet
going to be sound and that's going to
bring action upon this earth.
Now, one trumpet is going to bring uh uh
uh uh
cause the
west
to attack the east.
And they going to hit them with germ and
uh uh even germ or chemical warfare
because it says
you go Go to Revelation 9th chapter and
let's read this. Okay.
Because all of these
it all this take place when this
trumpet. I'm just going I'm just going
uh
We just going to go to Revelation 9th
chapter and deal with this one
uh case. Then let you know that all the
rest of them
are the same.
But not in one day.
You want to pick it up at verse 1?
That's right. Verse 1. Just read.
And the fifth angel sounded, and I saw a
star fall from heaven unto the earth.
And to him was given the key of the
bottomless pit. And he opened the
bottomless pit, and there arose a smoke
out of the pit, as the smoke of a great
furnace. And the sun and the air were
darkened by reason of the smoke of the
pit.
And there came out of the smoke locusts
upon the earth. And as of them was given
power, as the scorpions of the earth
have power.
And it was commanded them that they
should not hurt the grass of the earth,
neither any green thing, neither any
tree, only those men which have not the
seal of God in their foreheads.
How long was it with
How long did they do it?
He breathed.
And to them it was given that they
should not kill them, but but that they
should be tormented five months. And
their torment was as the torment of a
scorpion when he striketh a man.
And in those days shall men seek death
and shall not find it, and shall desire
to die, and death shall flee from them.
Now, that's that's under
That was under the fifth angel.
That's the fifth trumpet. Right.
>> So, between fifth and the sixth trumpet,
you have a minimum of five months.
Right.
So, you have time between all of them
because stuff had to happen with each
trumpet. So, no.
They They did not blow in one day.
Don't have to say.
All right. I want I want to say to the
to the young fellow, good question
there. Good question.
All right. We're going to move on to our
next one.
Next one. Manaya Tishbon says, "In the
spirit of Hallow's Eve, the public
school I work at will wear costumes,
paint pumpkins, and other activities
will take place.
What is the best way to handle this
wicked day disguised as seasonal?"
All right. The season is upon us.
Julius, look like you wanted to say
something.
Look like you just go go to work and do
your job. You ain't got to dress up if
it's not mandated.
That's it.
Don't make it personal.
Don't make it personal. Just go to work,
do your job.
Right.
Yeah.
All right. We're going to move on to our
next question.
Next one. Uh Skywriter asks, "How should
we pray?
Should we pray on knees and face in the
floor
or pray standing up?"
The choice belong to you.
That's it. Jonah prayed in the belly of
the whale. Yeah, so so did.
This is up to you.
Yep.
All right.
We rolling, Deborah, even though time is
rolling, too.
Yeah, okay. This next one here, amazing
Israelite
says, "Please give understanding to the
verse
Exodus 20 verse 12
and Galatians 4 verse 26 pertaining to
children who grow up in homes without
their dad or mom."
And then
then they have and
verse Matthew
12 verse 50.
Does the honor go to Jerusalem
above and who Jesus said
Okay, so these are two different
questions here. Right. So,
um
again,
uh
please give understanding to verse verse
Exodus 20 verse 12 and Galatians 4 verse
pertaining to children who grow up in
homes without their dad
or mom.
All right. There's There's three
scriptures there. We usually ask for a
two scripture
maximum there, but let's let's kick it
off with that Exodus 20 and 12 first,
Tenzil. By honoring your father and your
mother.
Go ahead, bro.
Honor thy father and thy mother, that
thy days may be long upon the land which
the Lord thy God giveth thee.
Open to the panel.
Now, that's that's do don't have any
kind
of addendum to it.
So, no matter where you grew up
in foster home, your father and your
mother left you, whatever,
you still have to honor them.
Yep. And God deals with them
for their faults.
It mean exactly what it said, whether
you in house or out, whether you grew up
in a foster child, or whether you grew
up in a well-kept family.
Scripture is the same. Honor your father
and your mother that you might that your
days might be long on earth.
It didn't say if they did this or if
they did that.
Yep.
What about Galatians now?
Yeah, Galatians.
>> Galatians 4 verse 26.
Read it.
But Jerusalem, which is above, is free,
which is the mother of us all.
That's the new Jerusalem. You find it in
Revelation 21st chapter.
That's the father's scripture.
That's all it's saying.
Yep.
All right. Now, let's go to that last
one, Deborah, in in Matthew. Yeah, so
then
um the person says, "Matthew 12 verse 50
does the honor go to Jerusalem above and
who Jesus said
Matthew 12
Yeah, uh
You know what? You should pick it up at
that 46, Tenzil, so we can get some
understanding
and read right into it. Go ahead, pick
it up at 46 and then let's open it up to
the panel. Go ahead.
While he yet talked to the people,
behold, his mother and his brethren
stood without, desiring to speak with
him.
Then one said unto him,
"Behold, thy mother and thy brother
stand without, desiring to speak with
thee." But he answered and said unto him
that told him,
"Who is my mother?
And who are my brethren?"
And he stretched forth his hand towards
his disciples and said, "Behold, my
mother and my brethren.
Mhm. Whosoever shall do the will of my
father which is in heaven,
the same is my brother and sister and
mother."
Yes. Whoever keepeth commandments.
Uh spiritual.
That don't That don't
uh uh
get rid of your biological
mother and father
and your brothers. All it's saying to
you that the people that keep God's
commandments, they're your spiritual
mother and your brothers, too.
Yes, sir.
Yep. All right.
Okay, Sister Deborah, we are down to our
last question or two. The next one.
All right.
Uh
so, Sam Burns says, "Is Revelation 18
verse 8
uh they want to know what Peter was
talking about because then they give 2
Peter 3 verse 8
and say a day as a thousand years.
Ha uh hard to see this happening in a
24-hour period."
So, first is Revelation 18 verse 8. They
want to know what Peter was talking
about and then they give 2 Peter 3 verse
8 stating about a day as a thousand year
and then they make this statement, "Hard
to see this happening in a 24-hour
period."
All right, let's shed some light and uh
pick it up at that Revelation 18
and verse 8.
Therefore shall her plagues come in one
day,
death and mourning and famine, and she
shall be utterly burnt with fire, for
strong is the Lord God who judgeth her.
All right. And then
Let's Let's call it
>> the great
Yeah.
He said that was during the great
tribulation, correct? Yes, sir. That is
correct.
All right. And now we're going to go
into that uh
What's that? 2 Peter?
Yeah, 2 Peter 3 verse 8.
But beloved,
be not ignorant of this one thing,
that one day is with the Lord as a
thousand years, and a thousand years
as one day.
All right, back to
>> say Yeah, so they say hard to see this
happening in a 24-hour period.
Hard to see what's happening in a
24-hour period?
Right.
>> Yeah.
Revelation 18 and 8.
Therefore her shall her plagues come in
one day,
death and mourning and famine.
This is even called the hour of
temptation, too.
It's still talking about 3 and 1/2
years. Yes. And it got nothing
for a thousand year day.
Yeah. Them two different precepts of the
same term.
A day.
Yep.
That's what the Lord called the hour of
temptation.
3 and 1/2 years, but it also
go on the
uh you know, uh uh
this also is talking about the time of
the great tribulation.
Mhm.
Right. And that 2 Peter 3 and 8 is in a
whole 'nother direction.
Right. It is.
Mhm. Because this is talking about
dealing
This 18 is talking about dealing with
Babylon the Great or either the beast
and false prophet, their organization.
Mhm. Got nothing to do with
Yep.
So.
Okay, well, we hope that that answered
your question as well. Uh time check,
please. Yes, the time is 9:02.
All right, 9:02. Well, we have ran out
of time and we want to thank everybody
from all around the world who tuned in
with us. That if you sent us a question
and we didn't get to it, please don't
resubmit it. Sister Deborah take your
question, put it in rotation, and we
will address it next week.
So, until we all come together again, be
safe, be blessed,
stay prayed up, and may the Lord have
mercy on us all as Brother Tenzil closes
us out.
Our Father, which art in heaven,
hallowed be thy name. Thy kingdom come,
thy will be done in earth, as it is in
heaven.
Give us this day our daily bread, and
forgive us of our debts, as we forgive
our debtors.
And lead us not into temptation, but
deliver us from evil. For thine is the
kingdom, and the power, and the glory
forever. In Jesus' name we pray.
Amen.